askactor.com 2014-11-11

# Welcome to ASK K-POP is the Ultimate Site for Kpop, Fanclubs,News,Images Community Entertainment

##  Privacy policy

ASKK-POP is committed to safeguarding the privacy of its audience. This Privacy Policy applies to solely to the information collected on ASKK-POP.com. ASKK-POP may periodically update and revise this policy. Be sure to visit this page in order to review the most current Privacy Policy.

ASKK-POP may be used without registering a user account. Users who wish to sign up for a free ASKK-POP.com account are only obligated to register a unique username and password. All other personal information is furnished optionally at the sole discretion of the end user to enhance their ASKK-POP experience.

## Information We Collect

ASKK-POP collects the following personal information via the user profile page (this information is not required by ASKK-POP and is provided at the sole discretion of the user):

  1. Personally identifiable information for display on the user's profile page. This information includes: first name, last name, birthdate, gender, im username, city, state and postal code as well as links to other personal websites (note that birthdate itself is not displayed, but age is).
  2. Personal information that is not displayed but used to enhance the user experience: email address. Email address is not published on the user profile but used for password recovery, activity alerts and periodic announcements from ASKK-POP.com (all of which the user can disable at any time). Email information is not sold or given to any 3rd parties and is used solely to improve the ASKK-POP.com experience.

ASKK-POP also allows users to post photos, participate in polls, submit content and articles, post on their wall, send private messages to friends and more. Such content is submitted at the sole discretion of the user. Personal information contained in this content may be archived and linked to the user's profile page.

Some information collected by ASKK-POP is not explicitly submitted by the user; we log your browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp.

ASKK-POP also integrates several 3rd party services including Facebook Connect, the Facebook Like Button and Meebo Chat which may collect and archive personal information. Please refer to the privacy policies for these respective services to learn more about their privacy policies as ASKK-POP has no control over the information they collect.

## How We Use Your Information

Information such as your full name, profile photo and any personally identifiable information you have included in your profile may be shown to friends or other users primarily in conjunction with content you have contributed. Your full name and email address may also be used when you send an email notification to a friend (such as in an invitation). We may also use your email address to send you updates or news regarding our site, but you may choose not to receive email of this type by editing your preferences in your profile. Additionally, we use your email address to contact you on behalf of your friends (such as when someone sends you a personal message).

ASKK-POP uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, 

Browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp data help us diagnose problems with our server, administer ASKK-POP, and otherwise provide the highest possible level of service to you. In addition, we use this information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, their advertising banners.

## Use of Cookies and Beacons

Like most websites, ASKK-POP requires cookies to function properly. Cookies are small text files that reside on a user's computer and identify you as a unique user. We use cookies to refine our site and simplify the user experience. For example, the use of cookies allows registered users to enter our site without explicitly typing in their email address and password every time.

You should be aware that ASKK-POP cannot control the use of cookies, beacons and flash cookies by 3rd party advertisers or any of the information advertisers may gather from their use of their cookies, beacons or flash cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of the aforementioned methos, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature as well as browser add-ons that can help you manage cookies and beacons while web browsing; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the ASKK-POP site.

## Security

Your ASKK-POP account is password-protected. ASKK-POP tries very hard to protect our users' information. We use industry standard measures to protect your information that is stored within our database. We limit the access to your information to those employees who need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

You hereby acknowledge that ASKK-POP is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

## Emails and Opt-out

Registered members can opt-out of personal messages initiated by friends and users, as well as opt-out of receiving notifications initiated by ASKK-POP (note: notification settings can be found under the your profile settings). Unregistered users that do not wish to receive emails may opt-out of receiving any communications by following the instructions contained in all emails.

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information. ASKK-POP will disclose information about individual users to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies, or to other individuals or entities in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes. Further, ASKK-POP may share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud, or to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of ASKK-POP, such as an acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, ASKK-POP will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

ASKK-POP will notify you when information about you may be provided to third parties in ways other than explained above, and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing.

## Controlling Your Personal Information

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) via comments, messages, forums, postings, or in other areas of the ASKK-POP network, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of ASKK-POP. Please do not post any personal information on the ASKK-POP site or in other areas that you expect to keep private.

As a registered ASKK-POP user, you can modify your personal information at any time by editing your "Profile". Also, upon your request, ASKK-POP will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally remove you and your personal information from the site; however, it may be impossible to remove your entry without some residual information being retained by ASKK-POP. Registered users who wish to close their account should contact info@askkpop.com.

## Links and Share

ASKK-POP does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy polices on these third party websites.

## Use of Cookies and Beacons

Like most websites, ASKK-POP requires cookies to function properly. Cookies are small text files that reside on a user's computer and identify you as a unique user. We use cookies to refine our site and simplify the user experience. For example, the use of cookies allows registered users to enter our site without explicitly typing in their email address and password every time.

You should be aware that ASKK-POP cannot control the use of cookies, beacons and flash cookies by 3rd party advertisers or any of the information advertisers may gather from their use of their cookies, beacons or flash cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of the aforementioned methos, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature as well as browser add-ons that can help you manage cookies and beacons while web browsing; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the ASKK-POP site.

## Terms and Contact

Terms and Modifications to this Privacy Statement

By using the website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the site. ASKK-POP may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the site indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Policy.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact info@askkpop.com.
